Indiana University Writers' Conference records, 1940-2009 C444
Indiana University Archives
- Writers' files, 1940-2004; undated (Box 1)
  - Sherwood, Frances, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Shore, Jane, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Shoup, Barbara, 1996-1998 (Box 4)
  - Sifton, Elisabeth, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Sigal, Clancy, 1977-1982 (Box 4)
  - Silber, Joan, 1986-1996 (Box 4)
  - Silko, Leslie Marmon, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Sissman, L.E., 1972 (Box 4)
  - Skeen, Pamela, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Slaughter, Frank G., 1964 (Box 4)
  - Smiley, Sam, 1968-1986 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Anne Mollegen, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Dave, 1982-1985 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Lillian, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Robert Paul, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Smith, S. Stephenson, 1941 (Box 4)
  - Smith, William Jay, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Snyder, Gary, 1975-1981 (Box 4)
  - Snodgrass, W.D., 1982 (Box 4)
  - Snyder, Mary Rennels, 1961-1965 (Box 4)
  - Solt, Mary Ellen, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Solwitz, Shawn, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Sparkes, Boyden, 1945-1946 (Box 4)
  - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1970-1973 (Box 5)
  - Spencer, Theodore, 1946-1947 (Box 5)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Spewack, Sam and Bella, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Spurgeon, Dickie, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - St. John, David, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Stafford, Jean, 1949 (Box 5)
  - Stafford, William, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  - Stambler, Peter, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Stanford, Ann, undated (Box 5)
  - Stanton, Maura, 1981-1993 (Box 5)
  - Stanton, Will, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
  - Stefanile, Felix, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Stegner, Wallace, 1941-1949 (Box 5)
  - Steinbeck, John, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Steingass, David, 1981-1982 (Box 5)
  - Stern, Ed, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Stern, Gerald, 1996; undated (Box 5)
  - Stevens, Wallace, 1949 (Box 5)
  - Stewart, Fred Mustard, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
  - Stone, Irving, 1948-1963 (Box 5)
  - Stong, Phil, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Strand, Mark, undated (Box 5)
  - Strode, Hudson, 1941-1948 (Box 5)
  - Strohm, P., 1980-1983 (Box 5)
  - Stryk, Lucien, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Stuart, Jesse, 1940-1955 (Box 5)
  - Styron, William, 1955-1964 (Box 5)
  - Suckow, Ruth, 1942-1947 (Box 5)
  - Swan, Gladys, 1984-1991 (Box 5)
  - Swann, Brian, 1979-1995 (Box 5)
  - Swann, Roberta, 1988-1995 (Box 5)
  - Swarthout, Glendon, 1958-1966 (Box 5)
  - Swenson, Karen, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Swenson, May, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - S – Misc. Letters, 1947-1964 (Box 5)
  - Talese, Gay, Nan A. Talese, Editor, Random House, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Tate, Allen, 1949-1950 (Box 5)
  - Taylor, Peter, 1950-1961 (Box 5)
  - Taylor, Robert Lewis, 1960-1968 (Box 5)
  - Terry, Megan, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Terkel, Studs, 1975-1980 (Box 5)
  - Tesich, Steve, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Thom, James Alexander, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Thompson, Jean, 1986-2004 (Box 5)
  - Troy, Judy, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Tillinghast, Richard, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Tribble, Jon, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Trilling, Lionel, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Truesdale, Bill, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Tunis, John R., 1946-1948 (Box 5)
  - Tyler, Anne, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Turco, Lewis, undated (Box 5)
  - Turner, Alberta, 1981-1982 (Box 5)
  - Twichell, Chase, 1984 (Box 5)
  - T – Misc. Letters, 1964-1976 (Box 5)
  - Ueland, Brenda, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Ullman, James Ramsey, 1956-1957 (Box 5)
  - Urdang, Constance, Donald Finkel, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Van Duyn, Mona, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Van Wert, Bill, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Vivante, Arturo, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Vogel, Paula, undated (Box 5)
  - Vogelsang, Arthur, 1986-1996 (Box 5)
  - Voigt, Ellen Bryant, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Volkman, Karen, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1961-1981 (Box 5)
  - V – Misc. Letters, 1941-1954 (Box 5)
  - Wagner, Dave, undated (Box 5)
  - Wagoner, David, 1959-1983 (Box 5)
  - Wain, John, undated (Box 5)
  - Wakoski, Diane, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
  - Walker, Alice, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Wallop, (John) Douglass, 1968-1972 (Box 5)
  - Ward, Mary Jane, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Warren, Robert Penn, 1946-1951 (Box 5)
  - Webb, Charles, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Weeks, Edward, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
  - Weidman, Jerome, 1964-1978 (Box 5)
  - Weil, Anne, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Weinberg, Dolores, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Weingarten, Roger, 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Weir, Ann Lowry, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Welty, Eudora, 1946-1961 (Box 5)
  - Wescott, Glenway, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
  - Wesker, Arnold, 1975 (Box 5)
  - West, Jessamyn, 1946-1960 (Box 5)
  - Westheimer, David, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Weston, John, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Weyr, Rhoda A., 1976-1980 (Box 5)
  - Wheeler, Harvey, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Whittemore, Reed, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Wilbur, Richard, 1954-1956 (Box 5)
  - Wiegner, Kathleen, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1945-1952 (Box 5)
  - Wilk, David, 1979-1981 (Box 5)
  - Willen, Eileen Davis, 1949-1950 (Box 5)
  - Williams, Ben Ames, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Williams, Oscar, 1951-1961 (Box 5)
  - Williams, Tennessee, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
  - Wilson, Lanford, undated (Box 5)
  - Wilson, Robley, 1979-1986 (Box 5)
  - Wilson, Victoria, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Wilson, William E., 1947-1949 (Box 5)
  - Wodehouse, P.G., 1962 (Box 5)
  - Woiwode, Larry, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Wojahn, David, 1985-1996 (Box 5)
  - Wojciechowska, Maia, 1969-1980 (Box 5)
  - Wolff, Tobias, 1984-1986 (Box 5)
  - Wolitzer, Hilma, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Woods, John, 1976-1981 (Box 5)
  - Wouk, Herman, 1951-1953 (Box 5)
  - Wylie, Laurence, 1958 (Box 5)
  - W – Misc. Letters (Box 5)
  - Yates, Elizabeth, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Yates, Richard, 1984-1989 (Box 5)
  - Young, Al, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Young, Dean, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Young, Karl, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Young, Marguerite, 1941-1965 (Box 5)
  - Young, Stanley, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Yurick, Sol, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
  - Zacharias, Lee, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Zelazny, Roger, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Zinsser, William K. (Box 5)
  - Zolotow, Charlotte, 1961-1975 (Box 5)
  - Zolotow, Maurice, 1958-1972 (Box 5)
  - Zwinger, Ann, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Zygas, Egle, 1981 (Box 5)
- Administrative Files, 1940-2009 (Box 5)
  - Ads – Examples, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Agents and Editors, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Blank Conference Award, undated (Box 5)
  - Bob McNutt's Notes on Running the Conference, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Brochure, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Brochure, 1981; 1983 (Box 5)
  - Brochure, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Brochure, 1996-1999 (Box 5)
  - Brochure, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Brochure Text, 1991-1994 (Box 5)
  - Budgeting and Funding, 1989-1994 (Box 6)
  - Budgeting and Funding, 1990-1993 (Box 6)
  - Catalogue of Literary Magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Conference Information Sheets, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Conference Flyers, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Conference Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Conference Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Conference Materials and Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box 6)
  - Conference Memos and Announcements, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence – Faculty Invite Letters, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence – Brad Senden, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence – Chairman, IU English, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence – Jan Susina re: Assistant Director Position, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence – Robert Mitchner, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Folder Example, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Lists, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Form Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Form Letters, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Form Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Guide to the Writers' Conference, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Guide to the Writers' Conference, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Index of Authors Invited, undated (Box 7)
  - IUWC Raves and Accomplishments, 1978-1980 (Box 7)
  - Lawyers for the Arts, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Literary Advocates Basics of Publishing Presentation Handouts, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Literary Advocates Correspondence, 2000 (Box 7)
  - "The Literary Agent" Handouts, 1977-1980 (Box 7)
  - Logo Materials, 1998; undated (Box 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - Mystery Writers of America Member List, undated (Box 7)
  - News Clippings, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - Other Writers' Conferences, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Participant Folder Example, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Participant Folder Example, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Participant Mailing Example, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference, undated (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Photos – Conference Staff, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Planning Documents, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Poetry Anthology of the Writers' Conference, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Poets and Writers Grant, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Posters, 1981-1985, 2003-2009, and undated; (oversize) (Box OS2)
  - Press Packet, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Press Releases, 1993-1995 (Box 7)
  - Press Releases and Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Press Releases and Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 7)
  - Publicity Examples, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - Publishing Resources, undated (Box 8)
  - Reorganization, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Schedule of Events, 1990-1992 (Box 8)
  - Schedule of Events, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Schedule of Readings, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Scholarships, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - Scholarships, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Search for Assistant Director, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Search for Assistant Director, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Summer Session Course Bulletins, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Writers' Conference History, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Writers' Conferences and Festivals Association, 1992-1994 (Box 8)
  - Writing in a Small Town Grant, 1985-1986 (Box 8)